

702 630 6976 AARONJLILLA@GMAIL.COM 8025 RUSSELL RD LAS VEGAS. NV 89113

DESIGN

PHOTOSHOP

C4D + OCTANE

ILLUSTRATOR

AFTER EFFECTS

LIGHTROOM

DEVELOPMENT SKILLS

HTML

Css

JAVASCRIPT

REACT.JS

NODE.JS

SASS

JQUERY

MONGODB

PHP & MYSQL

MWW.AARONLILLA.COM

ABOUT ME

Experienced web designer & full stack developer from Las Vegas, Nevada with over 6 years design experience and 2 years development experience. I excell and focus in front end user interfaces but also have a growing interest and proficiency in backend technologies. Trained in an assortment of front-end and backend technologies and specializing in javascript, as well as a multitude of design software for both 2D and 3D graphics and even animation. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate in a team setting.

WORK EXPERIENCE

05/2017 TO CURRENT

EVERGREEN ORGANIX

SUPERCRITICAL CO2 EXTRACTION CHEMIST

- Responsible for start to finish supercritical extraction of organic matter into high quality concentrate
- Distill crude concentrate using short path distillation
- Responsible for production run design to min-max yields depending on product quality
- Created Standard Operating Procedures and safety standards for main laboratory
- Prepared and executed all extraction and distillation of organic products to maximum capacity

02/2015 TO 05/2017

EVERGREEN ORGANIX

INVENTORY & PACKAGING MANAGER

- Responsible for tracking and maining a multi-million dollar inventory in a very fast paced environment
- Fulfilling and directing shipping of large orders
- Maintained software for tracking inventory as well as back-end system maintenance
- Managed a team of 6 successfully and improved overall efficiency
- Calculated top and bottom selling products to assist company in maximizing profits

06/2013 TO 02/2015

VEMAC CONSTRUCTION

LASER SCREED OPERATOR

- Responsible for grading slopes and paving large concrete lots with heavy machinery
- Maintained, repaired, and cleaned laser screed
- Used 3D software to create modeled representation of landscapes
- Perform daily maintenance and safety checks of equipment. Notify supervisor of any needed repairs.
- Assists in the general operation of each job site

06/2008 TO CURRENT

FREELANCE

WEB DESIGNER & DEVELOPER

- Planned, developed, tested, deployed, and maintained web applications
- Effectively translated client requirements into application designs and system requirements
- Writing cross-browser compliant HTML, CSS & JavaScript
- Creating logos, banners and buttons for websites
- Awareness of the Web Development industry, and new technologies.

EDUCATION

COLLEGE OF SOUTHERN NEVADA
ORGANIC CHEMISTRY

02/2010 - 05/2011 NO DEGREE

PALO VERDE HIGH SCHOOL LAS VEGAS, NV

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA